<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright 2024 pyamsoft
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at:
  ~
  ~     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
  <string name="expert_title">Expert Settings</string>
  <string
    name="expert_description"
  >This is for Advanced Users.\n\nAdjusting these options may completely change how %1$s performs, proceed at your own risk. Many users will NOT need to change these settings.</string>

  <string name="expert_power_balance_title">Power Balance</string>
  <string
    name="expert_power_balance_description"
  >This is for Advanced Users.\n\nYou can adjust the performance and resource usage of the %1$s Hotspot, which will adjust the number of virtual threads allocated to the Hotspot Network.\n\nMore Threads will result in usually faster performance, but higher battery usage and may heat up or slow down your device.</string>
  <string name="expert_power_balance_button">Adjust Power Balance</string>

  <string name="expert_balance_max_title">Max Performance</string>
  <string
    name="expert_balance_max_description"
  >Unlimited threads. Offers maximum performance. Throws battery usage concerns out the window.</string>
  <string name="expert_balance_super_save_title">Max Battery-Saving</string>
  <string
    name="expert_balance_super_save_description"
  >%1$d threads. Uses the least battery but offers the slowest hotspot performance.</string>
  <string name="expert_balance_save_title">Battery-Saving</string>
  <string
    name="expert_balance_save_description"
  >%1$d threads. Uses less battery but offers slower hotspot performance.</string>
  <string name="expert_balance_normal_title">Balanced</string>
  <string
    name="expert_balance_normal_description"
  >%1$d threads. Offers a balance between battery usage and hotspot performance.</string>
  <string name="expert_balance_performance_title">Performance</string>
  <string
    name="expert_balance_performance_description"
  >%1$d threads. Offers better hotspot performance at the cost of more battery usage.</string>
  <string
    name="expert_balance_super_performance_title"
  >High Performance</string>
  <string
    name="expert_balance_super_performance_description"
  >%1$d threads. Offers great hotspot performance at the cost of significant battery usage.</string>

  <!-- TODO Need translations -->
  <string name="expert_socket_timeout_title">Socket Timeout</string>
  <string
    name="expert_socket_timeout_description"
  >This is for Advanced Users.\n\nYou can adjust the timeout, which controls how long %1$s will wait for a connection before closing a socket. For most well behaving, modern websites on a decent connection, you should be fine with the default. If you notice connections are reporting frequent time outs, you should try increasing this value. If you notice high latency, you could try lowering the value</string>
  <string name="expert_socket_timeout_button">Adjust Socket Timeout</string>

  <string name="expert_timeout_yolo_title">No Timeout</string>
  <string
    name="expert_timeout_yolo_description"
  >Will never close connections until the website closes them. Throws memory usage and latency concerns out the window in an attempt to get websites to work. If there are many connections, could massively increase latency and memory usage. Adjusting Power Balance for Max or High performance is recommended.</string>
  <string name="expert_timeout_toofast_title">3 seconds</string>
  <string
    name="expert_timeout_toofast_description"
  >Barely waits at all. If you are on a fast connection, most well-behaved websites should still work. Cleans up aggressively, lowering memory usage and latency at the risk of breaking connections</string>
  <string name="expert_timeout_fast_title">10 seconds</string>
  <string
    name="expert_timeout_fast_description"
  >Slightly faster timeout that should work with most well-behaved websites. Slightly lower memory usage, and only some latency if there are many connections.</string>
  <string name="expert_timeout_balance_title">30 seconds</string>
  <string
    name="expert_timeout_balance_description"
  >The most balanced setting that should work with most well-behaved websites. Normal memory usage, and only some latency if there are many connections.</string>
  <string name="expert_timeout_conservative_title">1 minute</string>
  <string
    name="expert_timeout_conservative_description"
  >Waits extra long which should allow slower or bad behaving websites to still work. Slightly higher memory usage and latency if there are many connections. Adjusting Power Balance for High performance is recommended.</string>
  <string name="expert_timeout_longwait_title">5 minutes</string>
  <string
    name="expert_timeout_longwait_description"
  >Almost every website should work. If there are many connections, could massively increase latency and memory usage. Adjusting Power Balance for Max or High performance is recommended.</string>
</resources>
